0433 060 440 📞

sarapennysmith@gmail.com <a>





sarasmith.io #

Sara Smith (Drieman)

With a genuine passion for technology and a natural desire to learn, IT has been the perfect industry to keep me engaged and to motivate me to continue expanding my skills. Working with unique companies, I've had exposure to many cutting edge applications and technologies and am comfortable with cloud computing and research, through to corporate IT.



Experience

Operations Team Leader / Systems Administrator | eResearch SA

APRIL 2015 – MARCH 2019

- Leading and motivating a team of 5 in developing and delivering eResearch computing needs to researchers across South Australia and nationally.
- Contributed to the design and implementation of new platforms for Cloud (VMware), High Performance Computing (Slurm) and enterprise grade storage (Dell), including planning and executing the decommission of old services (OpenStack, HDS).
- Architected a Configuration Management system (Puppet) to automate new service deployments and to ensure configuration changes are timely and uniform across all environments.
- Regular reporting on Service Desk metrics and trends, which aided the design of proactive solutions and reduced system downtime.

Unix System Administrator / Service Desk Analyst | Santos Ltd

AUGUST 2012 - APRIL 2015

- Maintaining a large virtual and physical environment comprised of diverse Operating Systems.
- Using ITIL concepts to service the IT needs of the 30,000+ company staff.

Technical Solutions Rep II | HP Enterprise Services

JUNE 2010 – AUGUST 2012

• High volume phone based Service Desk providing first level IT support for all staff and executives.

Varied Customer Service roles | 2000 – 2010



Education

Red Hat System Administration I

OCTOBER 2014

University of South Australia | Computer Science

2009 - 2010



Skills

- Linux and Windows system administration
- Storage administration and configuration
- Cloud Computing; VMware and OpenStack
- High Performance Computing design, build and administration; Slurm, Torque/Maui
- SharePoint and O365 administration
- Bash and (intermediate) Python scripting and automation
- Active Directory and LDAP authentication
- Configuration Management; Puppet, Ansible, GitHub